{
    "id": "059fc45ebe184faba938e94ebfd0417f",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What are you thinking .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "at",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the person I was looking ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very easy to work …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very easy to talk …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not certain ………………. what I am supposed to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She enjoys being looked ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate being shouted …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She saved money ………………. giving up smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She rang me ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I half believe ……………….. life after death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed ……………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to see a big increase ………………. productivity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very impressed …………….. your work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}